<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">
        <template id="partner_bank_account_changed_template" >
            <p>Dear <t t-esc="user_name" />,<br/><br/>
            You receive this email because we would like to be sure that you are the person who changed the bank account 
            of partner <t t-esc="partner.name" />
            <t t-if="partner.company_id">
                in <t t-esc="partner.company_id.name" />
            </t>
            at <t t-esc="timestamp" />. If you don't remember doing such action, it means your user credentials might be in the hands of 
            a scammer. When they get user credentials, scammers common schemes are the following:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Changing the footer of your document layout to invite your customers to pay invoices on a scam bank account</li>
                <li>Changing the bank account(s) of the company (same purpose). </li>
                <li>Changing the bank account(s) fo your vendors so you pay your bills on a scam bank account. </li>
            </ul>
                
            <p>That's why you will receive warning mails like this each time one of those actions is performed.</p>
            <p>If you think you are victim of a scam:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Change your user password (use a strong one). Also check that you don't use the same password for other purposes 
                    as well. Those accounts could be compromised as well.</li>
                <li>Log in
                    <t t-if="partner.company_id">
                        company <t t-esc="partner.company_id.name" />
                    </t>
                    and have a look at partner <t t-esc="partner.name" />. Check if everything is correct with a particular focus on bank 
                    account numbers, make corrections where necessary.</li>
                <li>If you had to fix the bank account, then check that no bills were created (or worse, paid) between
                    <t t-esc="timestamp" /> and now. Contact your partner if necessary.</li>
            </ul>
        </template>

        <template id="user_email_changed_template">
            <p>Dear <t t-esc="changed_user.name" />,<br/><br/>
                Your email was modified on <t t-esc="timestamp" /> by user <t t-esc="user.name" />.
                <t t-esc="old_email"/> --> <t t-esc="changed_user.email" />.
                <t t-if="user == changed_user" >
                    If you don't remember doing such change, your account credential might be in wrong hands.
                </t>
                <t t-else="">
                    If you don't know why <t t-esc="user.name" /> did this change, contact <t t-esc="user.name" />.
                    If it appears that <t t-esc="user.name" /> didn't do this change, your account credentials might be in wrong hands.
                </t>
            </p>
        </template>



        <template id="document_layout_changed_template">
            <p>Dear <t t-esc="user_name"/>,<br/><br/>
            You receive this email because we would like to be sure that you are the person who changed the document 
            template of company <t t-esc="company_name" /> at <t t-esc="timestamp" />. If you don't remember doing such 
            action, it means your user credentials might be in the hands of a scammer. When they get user credentials,
            scammers common schemes are the following:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Changing the footer of your document layout to invite your customers to pay invoices on a scam bank account.</li>
                <li>Changing the bank account(s) of the company (same purpose).</li>
                <li>Changing the bank account(s) for your vendors so you pay your bills on a scam bank account.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <p>That's why you will receive warning mails like this each time one of those actions is performed.
            If you think you are victim of a scam:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Change your user password (use a strong one). Also check that you don't use the same password 
                    for other purposes as well. Those accounts could be compromised as well.</li>
                <li>Log in company <t t-esc="company_name" /> and have a look on the document layout in the general settings.
                    Check if everything is correct with a particular focus on bank account numbers displayed
                    and make corrections where necessary.</li>
                <li>If you had to fix the document layout, then check no sales invoices were sent between <t t-esc="timestamp" /> and now.
                    Contact your customers if necessary.</li>
            </ul>
        </template>

    </data>
</odoo>
